Jimmy roach wants you to go into
business with him he says that whole
misunderstanding with the receiver of
Revenue is now dead and buried in a
forest Jimmy says he's got a real winner
of a proposition if it succeeds you'll
be printing money like his Uncle Arty
used to do before he accidentally tied
himself to a bowling ball and fell into
a swamp Jimmy says he needs the money up
front though just to smooth over some
rough edges who happen to go by the
names of Lucky Eddie and Knuckles McGee
Jimmy says it's enough for you can't
refuse Jimmy says you're about to hit
the big time in the face with a crowbar
there are many ways to grow your wealth
but we only believe in one consistency
credential consistency is the only
currency that matters credential as a
licensed financial services provider